Class of 1943 Records, 1939-2003
Smith College Archives
Class of 1943 Records
1939-2003
Smith College. Class of 1943.
RG 80 UUID:f7921499-303d-4ae0-85ef-8fe9ceb73367
8 boxes (6.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1943.
Historical Note
The Class of 1943 was the sixty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1943 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1943, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1943 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Fund Agent Letters 1953-1990 (Box 2139, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Last Chapel 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 4)
- Commencement Speaker 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 5)
- Class Dinner 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 6)
- Float Night 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1939-1940 (Box 2139, Folder 8)
- General 1940 (Box 2139, Folder 9)
- Groups 1939-1943, 1964-1965, 1984, 1991,n.d. (Box 2139, Folder 10)
- Hoop Rolling 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom 1942 (Box 2139, Folder 13)
- Junior Ushers 1942 (Box 2139, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1948-2003 (Box 2139, Folder 15)
- Mascot 1953 (Box 2139, Folder 16)
- Class Officers 1967-1993 (Box 2139, Folder 17)
- Class Officers-Photographs 1940 (Box 2139, Folder 18)
- Rally Day 1943 (Box 2139, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 2139, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1953-1958 (Box 2139, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 2139, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 2139, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1973 (Box 2139, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 2139, Folder 25)
- Reunions 1983 (Box 2139, Folder 26)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 2139, Folder 27)
- Reunions-Photographs 1988 (Box 2139, Folder 28)
- Reunions 1993 (Box 2139.1, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1998 (Box 2139.1, Folder 2)
- Reunions 2003 (Box 2139.1, Folder 3)
- Reunions-Accounts of 60th Reunion 2003 (Box 2139.1, Folder 4)
- Rules and Regulations 1942-1943 (Box 2139.1, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary (See OV) (Box 2139.1, Folder 6)
- Songs 1943 (Box 2139.1, Folder 7)
- Sophomore Carnival 1941 (Box 2139.1, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1941 (Box 2139.1, Folder 9)
- War Service 1943-1945 (Box 2139.1, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbook 1943-1946, 1962-1968 (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbook-Reunion Pictures 1958-1988 (Box OV)
- Reunion Scrapbooks 1948 (Box OV)
- Reunion Scrapbooks 1963 (Box OV)